<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kmail.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kmail</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMailxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      KMail is the email component of Kontact, the integrated personal information manager from KDE.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMail is de e-mailcomponent van Kontact, de geïntegreerde persoonlijke informatiebeheerder uit KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMail é o componente de e-mail do Kontact, o gestor de informações pessoais do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KMail é o componente de e-mail do Kontact, o gerenciador integrado de informações pessoais do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMail je e-mailový komponent programu Kontact, integrovaný správca osobných informácií z KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kmail är e-postkomponenten i Kontact, den integrerade personliga informationshanteraren från KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMail — компонент для роботи з електронною поштою комплексу програм Kontact, інтегрованого рішення для роботи з особистими даними у KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMail is the email component of Kontact, the integrated personal information manager from KDE.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supports the standard mail protocols IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt de standaard e-mailprotocollen IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta os protocolos-padrão de correio electrónico IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte aos padrões de protocolo de e-mail IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje štandardné mailové protokoly IMAP, POP3 a SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder standardprotokollen för e-post IMAP, POP3 och SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка роботи зі стандартними протоколами обміну електронною поштою, IMAP, POP3 та SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports the standard mail protocols IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.xx</li>
      <li>Supports authentication via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) and GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt authenticatie via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) en GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a autenticação por NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e por GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a autenticação por NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e por GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje overenie cez NTLM (Microsoft Windows) a GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder behörighetskontroll via NTLM (Microsoft WIndows) och GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка можливостей розпізнавання за допомогою NTLM (Microsoft Windows) та GSSAPI (Kerberos);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports authentication via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) and GSSAPI (Kerberos)xx</li>
      <li>Supports plain text and secure logins, using SSL and TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt platte tekst en veilig aanmelden met SSL en TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a autenticação por texto simples e segura, usando o SSL e o TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a autenticação segura e por texto simples, usando SSL e TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje čisté textové a zabezpečené prihlásenia, pomocou SSL a TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder vanlig text och säkra inloggningar, genom att använda SSL och TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка передавання реєстраційних даних звичайним текстом та шифрованими даними за допомогою SSL та TLS;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports plain text and secure logins, using SSL and TLS.xx</li>
      <li>Integration of international character sets and spell-checking (as-you-type and on demand)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integratie van internationale tekensets en spellingcontrole (terwijl-u-typt en op aanvraag)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração dos conjuntos de caracteres internacionais e a verificação ortográfica (à medida que escreve ou a pedido)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração dos conjuntos de caracteres internacionais e verificação ortográfica (enquanto escreve ou por solicitação)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrácia medzinárodných znakových sád a kontroly pravopisu (ako píšete a na požiadanie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrering av internationella teckenuppsättningar och stavningskontroll (medan man skriver och på begäran)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудована можливість роботи з даними у різних кодуваннях та перевірки правопису (інтерактивної та на вимогу);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegration of international character sets and spell-checking (as-you-type and on demand)xx</li>
      <li>Native support for inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, and S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ingebouwde ondersteuning voor inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME en S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte nativo e incorporado para o OpenPGP, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte nativo e integrado para OpenPGP, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Natívna podpora pre vstavané OpenPGP, PGP/MIME a S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbyggt stöd för OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, och S/MIME på plats.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудована підтримка OpenPGP, PGP/MIME та S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNative support for inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, and S/MIME.xx</li>
      <li>Reading and writing of HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lezen en schrijven van HTML-e-mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Leitura e escrita de mensagens em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Leitura e gravação de e-mails em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Čítanie a písanie HTML mailov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Läsa och skriva HTML-brev.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість читання та створення повідомлень з використанням коду HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxReading and writing of HTML mail.xx</li>
      <li>Ability to display plain text only from an HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheid om alleen gewone tekst te laten zien uit een HTML-e-mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidade de apresentar apenas o texto simples de uma mensagem em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidade de exibir apenas o texto simples de um e-mail em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosť zobraziť iba čistý text z HTML mailu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att bara visa vanlig text för ett HTML-brev.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість перегляду лише текстової частини з повідомлень у форматі HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAbility to display plain text only from an HTML mail.xx</li>
      <li>Allows you to receive and accept invitations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Stelt u in staat uitnodigingen te ontvangen en accepteren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Permite-lhe receber e aceitar convites.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permite-lhe receber e aceitar convites.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Umožní vám prijať a prijímať pozvánky.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Låter dig ta emot och acceptera inbjudningar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість отримувати та приймати запрошення;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAllows you to receive and accept invitations.xx</li>
      <li>Integration with popular spam checkers, e.g. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integratie met populaire spamcheckers, bijv. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração com as verificações de lixo electrónico, p.ex. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração com programas de verificação de spam, como o SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrácia s populárnymi kontrolami spamu, napr. SmamAssassin, Bogofilter, atď.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrering med populära skräppostkontrollprogram, t.ex. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">інтеграція з популярними системами захисту від небажаної кореспонденції, зокрема SpamAssassin, Bogofilter тощо;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegration with popular spam checkers, e.g. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.xx</li>
      <li>An optional spam probability meter can be displayed</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Een optionele waarschijnlijkheidsmeter voor spam kan getoond worden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode ser apresentado um medidor de probabilidades de lixo electrónico</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pode ser apresentado um medidor de probabilidades de spam</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Je možné zobraziť voliteľný meter pravdepodobnosti spamu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">En valfri sannolikhetsmätare för skräppost kan visas</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість показу оцінки ймовірності небажаності повідомлення;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAn optional spam probability meter can be displayedxx</li>
      <li>Powerful search and filter abilities</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Krachtige zoek en filter mogelijkheden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidades poderosas de pesquisa e filtragem</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidades pesquisa e filtragem poderosas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Silné schopnosti hľadania a filtrovania</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kraftfulla sök- och filtreringsmöjligheter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">потужні можливості з пошуку та фільтрування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPowerful search and filter abilitiesxx</li>
      <li>Can import mail from many other clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan e-mail importeren uit vele andere clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Poderá importar o correio a partir de muitos outros clientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importação de e-mails de muitos outros clientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Môže importovať mail z mnohých iných klientov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan importera brev från många andra program</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість імпортувати дані пошти з багатьох інших програм для роботи з електронною поштою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan import mail from many other clientsxx</li>
      <li>Searching in IMAP folders fully supported</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">In IMAP-mappen zoeken wordt volledig ondersteund</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A pesquisa nas pastas de IMAP é totalmente suportada</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte completo para pesquisa em pastas IMAP</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hľadanie v IMAP priečinokoch je plne podporované</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständigt stöd för sökning i IMAP-korgar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка повноцінного пошуку у теках IMAP;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSearching in IMAP folders fully supportedxx</li>
      <li>Highly integrated with other Kontact components</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hoge graad van integratie met andere componenten van Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Altamente integrado com os outros componentes do Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Altamente integrado com os outros componentes do Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vysoko integrovaný s inými komponentmi Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Helt integrerad med andra Kontact-komponenter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">високий рівень інтеграції з іншими компонентами Kontact;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxHighly integrated with other Kontact componentsxx</li>
      <li>Encrypted password saving in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opslaan van versleuteld wachtwoord in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gravação das senhas encriptadas na KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Salvamento das senhas criptografadas no KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ukladanie šifrovaných hesiel v KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Krypterat lösenord sparas i plånboken</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">зберігання зашифрованих реєстраційних даних за допомогою KWallet;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEncrypted password saving in KWalletxx</li>
      <li>Flagging and tagging of messages to aid sorting and recovery of information</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vlaggen en tags aanbrengen bij berichten om te helpen bij sorteren en herstel van informatie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Marcação e classificação de mensagens para ajudar a ordenar e a recuperar informações</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Marcação e classificação de mensagens para ajudar a ordenar e recuperar informações</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Označovanie a značkovanie správ na podporu triedenia a využitia informácií</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flaggning och etikettering av brev för att hjälpa till att sortera och återhämta information</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість додавання прапорців і міток до повідомлень з метою спрощення упорядковування та відновлення інформації;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFlagging and tagging of messages to aid sorting and recovery of informationxx</li>
      <li>Supports mailing list management features</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt functies voor discussielijstbeheer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta funcionalidades de gestão de listas de correio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a funcionalidades de gerenciamento de listas de discussão</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora funkcií správy mailing listov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder funktioner för hantering av sändlistor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка можливостей з керування повідомленнями зі списків листування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports mailing list management featuresxx</li>
      <li>Can replace text smilies with emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan smilies in de tekst vervangen door emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode substituir ícones emotivos de texto por gráficos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Substituição carinhas de texto por emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vie nahradiť textové smajlíky emotikonmi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan ersätta textsmilisar med ikoner</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість заміни текстових емоційок (смайликів) зображеннями;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan replace text smilies with emoticonsxx</li>
      <li>Displays the sender's picture or avatar if present in the address book</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Toont de foto of avatar van de afzender indien aanwezig in het adresboek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mostra a imagem ou avatar do remetente, caso esteja presente no livro de endereços</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Mostra a imagem ou avatar do remetente, caso esteja presente no livro de endereços</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zobrazí obrázok odosielateľa alebo avatar, ak je dostupny v adresári kontaktov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visar avsändarens bild eller avatar om den finns i adressboken</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість показу знімка або аватара відправника, якщо його визначено у адресній книзі;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplays the sender's picture or avatar if present in the address bookxx</li>
      <li>Supports X-Face (b/w pictures in messages)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt X-Face (z/w plaatjes in berichten)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta o X-Face (imagens a p/b nas mensagens)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta a X-Face (imagens em preto e branco nas mensagens)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje X-Face (č/b obrázky v správach)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder X-Face (svartvita bilder i brev)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка X-Face (чорно-білих зображень у повідомленнях);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports X-Face (b/w pictures in messages)xx</li>
      <li>Compression of attachments</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Compressie van bijlagen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Compressão dos anexos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Compressão dos anexos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kompresia príloh</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Komprimering av bilagor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість стискання долучень безпосередньо з вікна програми;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCompression of attachmentsxx</li>
      <li>KMail supports Groupware functionality.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">KMail ondersteunt Groupware functionaliteit.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">O KMail suporta as funcionalidades de trabalho em grupo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a funcionalidades de Groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">KMail podporuje funkcionalitu Groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kmail stöder grupprogramfunktioner.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка роботи у групах.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxKMail supports Groupware functionality.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmail</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kmail/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kmail.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmail</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
