<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kmail2.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">بريدك</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑пошта</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑pošta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑пошта</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑pošta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kmail</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMailxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KMail</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KMail</name>
  <summary>Email application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aplicació de correu electrònic</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació de correu electrònic</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">E-mailová aplikace</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">E-Mail-Programm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aplicación de correo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Sähköpostisovellus.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Application de messagerie électronique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Programma di posta elettronica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">E-mailtoepassing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Aplikacja pocztowa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Aplicação de e-mail</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Програм за е‑пошту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Program za e‑poštu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Програм за е‑пошту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Program za e‑poštu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">E-postprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Eposta uygulaması</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для роботи з електронною пошти</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxEmail applicationxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">电子邮件应用程序</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KMail is the email component of Kontact, the integrated personal information manager from KDE.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">«بريدك» هو مكوّن البريد ل‍«تراسلك»، مدير المعلومات الشّخصيّة المتكامل لكدي.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMail és el component de correu electrònic del Kontact, el gestor per a la informació personal integrat del KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KMail és el component de correu electrònic del Kontact, el gestor per a la informació personal integrat del KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMail ist die E-Mail-Komponente von Kontact, der integrierten persönlichen Informationsverwaltung für KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMail is the email component of Kontact, the integrated personal information manager from KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KMail es el componente de correo de Kontact, el gestor integrado de información personal de KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KMail on Kontacti ehk KDE lõimitud isikliku teabe halduri e-posti komponent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KMail on Kontactin, KDE:n henkilökohtaisen tiedonhallintajärjestelmän, sähköpostiosa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KMail est le composant pour le courrier électronique de la suite Kontact, le gestionnaire d'informations personnelles de KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KMail é o compoñente de correo electrónico de Kontact, o xestor completo de información persoal de KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KMail a Kontact, a KDE integrált információkezelő alkalmazásának e-mail programja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KMail è il componente di posta elettronica di Kontact, il gestore integrato di informazioni personali da KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KMail은 KDE 개인 정보 관리자 Kontact의 이메일 구성 요소입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">KMail yra Kontact, KDE integruotos asmeninės informacijos tvarkyklės, pašto komponentas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">KMail er e-postkomponenten i Kontact, KDEs integrerte personlige informasjonsbehandler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KMail is de Nettpostkomponent vun Kontact, KDE sien inbuut Pleger för persöönlich Informatschonen</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMail is de e-mailcomponent van Kontact, de geïntegreerde persoonlijke informatiebeheerder uit KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KMail jest składnikiem pocztowym pakietu Kontact, programu do zarządzania informacjami osobistymi w KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMail é o componente de e-mail do Kontact, o gestor de informações pessoais do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KMail é o componente de e-mail do Kontact, o gerenciador integrado de informações pessoais do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KMail — почтовый клиент в составе электронного секретаря Kontact от сообщества KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMail je e-mailový komponent programu Kontact, integrovaný správca osobných informácií z KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KMail je sestavni del paketa Kontact, ki omogoča delo z e-pošto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">К‑пошта је е‑поштанска компонента Контакта, КДЕ‑овог интегрисаног менаџера личних података.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑pošta je e‑poštanska komponenta Kontacta, KDE‑ovog integrisanog menadžera ličnih podataka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑пошта је е‑поштанска компонента Контакта, КДЕ‑овог интегрисаног менаџера личних података.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑pošta je e‑poštanska komponenta Kontacta, KDE‑ovog integrisanog menadžera ličnih podataka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kmail är e-postkomponenten i Kontact, den integrerade personliga informationshanteraren från KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KMail, Kontact'ın e-posta bileşeni ve aynı zamanda KDE'den tümleşik kişisel bilgi yöneticisidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMail — компонент для роботи з електронною поштою комплексу програм Kontact, інтегрованого рішення для роботи з особистими даними у KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMail is the email component of Kontact, the integrated personal information manager from KDE.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Kmail 是 KDE 集成个人信息管理器 Kontact 的电子邮件组件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KMail 是 Kontact 的電子郵件組件。Kontact 是 KDE 中的一套整合個人資訊管理員。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ypatybės:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Egenskaper:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supports the standard mail protocols IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم ميفاقات البريد القياسيّة IMAP، وPOP3 وSMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet els protocols de correu estàndards: IMAP, POP3 i SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet els protocols de correu estàndards: IMAP, POP3 i SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt die E-Mail-Standardprotokoll IMAP, POP3 und SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports the standard mail protocols IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa los protocolos estándar de correo IMAP, POP3 y SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Standardsete e-posti protokollide IMAP. POP3 ja SMTP toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee standardeja sähköpostiyhteyskäytäntöjä IMAP, POP3 ja SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des protocoles standards de messagerie IMAP, POP3 et SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatíbel cos protocolos de correo estándar: IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Standard levelező protokollok (IMAP, POP3, SMTP) támogatása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta i protocolli di posta standard IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">IMAP, POP3, SMTP 표준 메일 프로토콜을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Palaiko standartinius pašto protokolus tokius, kaip IMAP, POP3 ir SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Støtter standard e-post-protokollene IMAP, POP3 og SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt de Standard-Nettpostprotokollen IMAP, POP3 un SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt de standaard e-mailprotocollen IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa standardowych protokołów pocztowych IMAP, POP3 oraz SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta os protocolos-padrão de correio electrónico IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte aos padrões de protocolo de e-mail IMAP, POP3 e SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка распространённых почтовых протоколов IMAP, POP3 и SMTP;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje štandardné mailové protokoly IMAP, POP3 a SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira standardne poštne protokole: IMAP, POP3 in SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за стандардне поштанске протоколе ИМАП, ПОП3 и СМТП.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za standardne poštanske protokole IMAP, POP3 i SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за стандардне поштанске протоколе ИМАП, ПОП3 и СМТП.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za standardne poštanske protokole IMAP, POP3 i SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder standardprotokollen för e-post IMAP, POP3 och SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">IMAP, POP3 ve SMTP standart posta protokollerini destekler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка роботи зі стандартними протоколами обміну електронною поштою, IMAP, POP3 та SMTP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports the standard mail protocols IMAP, POP3 and SMTP.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持标准邮件协议 IMAP、POP3 和 SMTP。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支持標準郵件協定，如 IMAP, POP3 與 SMTP</li>
      <li>Supports authentication via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) and GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم الاستيثاق عبر NTLM (مايكروسوفت وندوز) وGSSAPI (كيربيروس)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet l'autenticació a través de NTLM (Microsoft Windows) i GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet l'autenticació a través de NTLM (Microsoft Windows) i GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt Authentifizierung mit NTLM (Microsoft Windows) und GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports authentication via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) and GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa la autenticación vía NTLM (Microsoft Windows) y GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Autentimise toetus NTLM (Microsoft Windows) ja GSSAPI (Kerberos) vahendusel</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee tunnistautumista NTLM:llä (Microsoft Windows) ja GSSAPIlla (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de l'authentification NTLM (Microsoft Windows) et GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite autenticarse mediante NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e GSSAPI (Kerberos).</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">NTLM (Microsoft Windows) és GSSAPI (Kerberos) hitelesítés támogatása</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta l'autenticazione tramite NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">NTLM(Microsoft Windows) 및 GSSAPI(Kerberos) 인증 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Støtter autentisering via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) og GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt de Identiteetprööv över NTLM (Windows) un GSSAPI (Kerberos).</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt authenticatie via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) en GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa uwierzytelniania przez NTLM (Microsoft Windows) oraz GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a autenticação por NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e por GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a autenticação por NTLM (Microsoft Windows) e por GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка аутентификации с помощью NTLM (Microsoft Windows) и GSSAPI (Kerberos);</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje overenie cez NTLM (Microsoft Windows) a GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira overjanje preko NTLM (Microsoft Windows) in GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Аутентификација преко НТЛМ‑а (Виндоуз) и ГССАПИ‑ја (кербер).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Autentifikacija preko NTLM‑a (Windows) i GSSAPI‑ja (Kerberos).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Аутентификација преко НТЛМ‑а (Виндоуз) и ГССАПИ‑ја (кербер).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Autentifikacija preko NTLM‑a (Windows) i GSSAPI‑ja (Kerberos).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder behörighetskontroll via NTLM (Microsoft WIndows) och GSSAPI (Kerberos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">NTLM (Microsoft Windows) ve GSSAPI (Kerberos) aracılığıyla kimlik doğrulamayı destekler</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка можливостей розпізнавання за допомогою NTLM (Microsoft Windows) та GSSAPI (Kerberos);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports authentication via NTLM (Microsoft Windows) and GSSAPI (Kerberos)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持使用 NTLM（Microsoft Windows）和 GSSAPI（Kerberos）的验证。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援透過 NTLM（Microsoft Windows）與 GSSAPI（Kerberos）認證</li>
      <li>Supports plain text and secure logins, using SSL and TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم النّصوص الصّرفة والولوجات الآمنة، باستخدام SSL وTLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet accés en text pla i segur, usant SSL i TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet accés en text pla i segur, usant SSL i TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt einfachen Text und sichere Anmeldung durch SSL und TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports plain text and secure logins, using SSL and TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa inicios de sesión con texto sin formato y cifrado SSL y TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lihttekstiga ja turvalise sisselogimise toetus SSL ja TLS abil</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee salaamatonta ja salattua kirjautumista (SSL:llä ja TLS:llä).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des identifications en texte clair ou sécurisées par SSL ou TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite identificarse mediante texto simple ou de forma segura, usando SSL e TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Sima szöveges és biztonságos bejelentkezés támogatása SSL és TLS használatával.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta testo semplice e login sicuri tramite SSL e TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">일반 텍스트, SSL/TLS 보안 로그인을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Støtter innlogging med ren tekst og sikker innlogging med SSL og TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt dat Anmellen mit Eenfachtext un mit seker SSL un TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt platte tekst en veilig aanmelden met SSL en TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa logowania przy użyciu zwykłego tekstu oraz bezpiecznego poprzez SSL i TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a autenticação por texto simples e segura, usando o SSL e o TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a autenticação segura e por texto simples, usando SSL e TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка аутентификации с пересылкой регистрационных данных как открытым текстом, так и безопасным образом с помощью SSL и TLS;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje čisté textové a zabezpečené prihlásenia, pomocou SSL a TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira prijavo z navadnim besedilom ali varno prijavo s pomočjo SSL in TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Обичнотекстуално и безбедно пријављивање, преко ССЛ‑а и ТЛС‑а.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Običnotekstualno i bezbedno prijavljivanje, preko SSL‑a i TLS‑a.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Обичнотекстуално и безбедно пријављивање, преко ССЛ‑а и ТЛС‑а.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Običnotekstualno i bezbedno prijavljivanje, preko SSL‑a i TLS‑a.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder vanlig text och säkra inloggningar, genom att använda SSL och TLS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Düz metin ve SSL ile TLS kullanarak güvenli girişleri destekler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка передавання реєстраційних даних звичайним текстом та шифрованими даними за допомогою SSL та TLS;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports plain text and secure logins, using SSL and TLS.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持纯文本和安全登录，使用 SSL 和 TLS。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援純文字與透過 SSL 與 TLS安全登入</li>
      <li>Integration of international character sets and spell-checking (as-you-type and on demand)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تكامل أطقم المحارف العالميّة وتدقيق الهجاء (عند الكتابة وعند الطّلب)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Integra els jocs de caràcters internacionals i la verificació ortogràfica (mentre escriviu i sota demanda)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integra els jocs de caràcters internacionals i la verificació ortogràfica (mentre escriviu i sota demanda)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Integration von internationalen Zeichensätzen und einer Rechtschreibprüfung bei der Eingabe oder auf Anforderung</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Integration of international character sets and spell-checking (as-you-type and on demand)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración de juegos de caracteres internacionales y revisión ortográfica (mientras-se-teclea y bajo demanda)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rahvusvaheliste märgistike ja õigekirja kontrolli lõimimine (viimane valikuliselt kas kirjutamise ajal või nõudmisel)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee kansainvälisiä merkistöjä ja oikolukua (kirjoittaessasi tai pyydettäessä)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégration des ensembles de caractères et correcteurs orthographiques internationaux (pendant la saisie et à la demande)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Integración con xogos de caracteres internacionais e corrección ortográfica (a medida que escribe ou iniciada explicitamente).</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Nemzetközi karakterkészletek és helyesírás-ellenőrzés integrációja</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Integrazione di insiemi di caratteri e correttore ortografico internazionali (durante la digitazione e su richiesta).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 문자 인코딩과 맞춤법 검사(입력하는 즉시 및 전체 텍스트) 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Internasjonale tegnsett og stavekontroll er integrert. Stavekontroll fortløpende eller på forespørsel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Inbuut internatschonaal Tekensetten un Schriefwiesprööv (bi't Tippen un op Anföddern)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integratie van internationale tekensets en spellingcontrole (terwijl-u-typt en op aanvraag)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Integracja międzynarodowych zestawów znaków i sprawdzania pisowni (w trakcie pisania i na żądanie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração dos conjuntos de caracteres internacionais e a verificação ortográfica (à medida que escreve ou a pedido)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração dos conjuntos de caracteres internacionais e verificação ortográfica (enquanto escreve ou por solicitação)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка множества кодировок текста и проверки орфографии (на лету или по запросу);</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrácia medzinárodných znakových sád a kontroly pravopisu (ako píšete a na požiadanie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira mednarodne nabore znakov in preverjanje črkovanja (med tipkanjem in na zahtevo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Међународна кодирања и провера правописа (током куцања и на захтев).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Međunarodna kodiranja i provera pravopisa (tokom kucanja i na zahtev).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Међународна кодирања и провера правописа (током куцања и на захтев).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Međunarodna kodiranja i provera pravopisa (tokom kucanja i na zahtev).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrering av internationella teckenuppsättningar och stavningskontroll (medan man skriver och på begäran)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Uluslararası karakter kümeleri ve yazım denetimi (yazarken veya isteğe bağlı) tümleştirmesi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудована можливість роботи з даними у різних кодуваннях та перевірки правопису (інтерактивної та на вимогу);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegration of international character sets and spell-checking (as-you-type and on demand)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">集成国际字符集支持和拼写检查（输入即检查，可以按照需求配置）</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">整合國際字元集與拼字檢查（輸入時即時檢查）</li>
      <li>Native support for inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, and S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">دعم أصيل ل‍OpenPGP، وPGP/MIME وS/MIME ضمن السّياق.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació nativa per a OpenPGP, PGP/MIME i S/MIME inclòs.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementació nativa per a OpenPGP, PGP/MIME i S/MIME inclòs.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Native Unterstützung für Inline-OpenPGP, PGP/MIME und S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Native support for inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, and S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación nativa de OpenPGP, PGP/MIME y S/MIME intercalados.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Sisemise OpenPGP, PGP/MIME ja S/MIME sisseehitatud toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee natiivisti sisällytettyä OpenPGP:tä, PGP/MIMEä ja S/MIMEä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge intégrée du chiffrement en ligne OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, et S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade nativa con OpenPGP, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Natív támogatás beágyazott OpenPGP-hez, PGP/MIME-hoz és S/MIME-hoz.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto nativo per OpenPGP in linea, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">부가 기능 없이 인라인 OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, S/MIME을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Innebygget støtte for OpenPGP, PGP/MIME og S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Inbuut Ünnerstütten för OpenPGP, PGP/MIME un S/MIME</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ingebouwde ondersteuning voor inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME en S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Bezpośrednia obsługa dla OpenPGP w treści, PGP/MIME oraz S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte nativo e incorporado para o OpenPGP, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte nativo e integrado para OpenPGP, PGP/MIME e S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Встроенная поддержка OpenPGP, PGP/MIME и S/MIME в тексте письма;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Natívna podpora pre vstavané OpenPGP, PGP/MIME a S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ima lastno podporo znotrajvrstičnim OpenPGP, PGP/MIME in S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Самосвојна подршка за уткани опенПГП, ПГП/МИМЕ и С/МИМЕ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Samosvojna podrška za utkani OpenPGP, PGP/MIME i S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Самосвојна подршка за уткани опенПГП, ПГП/МИМЕ и С/МИМЕ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Samosvojna podrška za utkani OpenPGP, PGP/MIME i S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbyggt stöd för OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, och S/MIME på plats.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Satıriçi OpenPGP, PGP/MIME ve S/MIME için doğal destek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудована підтримка OpenPGP, PGP/MIME та S/MIME.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNative support for inline OpenPGP, PGP/MIME, and S/MIME.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">对内联 OpenPGP、PGP/MIME 和 S/MIME 的原生支持。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援內含式 OpenPGP, PGP/MIME 與  S/MIME</li>
      <li>Reading and writing of HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">قراءة بريد HTML وكتابته.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Lectura i escriptura d'un correu HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Lectura i escriptura d'un correu HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Lesen und Schreiben von HTML-E-Mails.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Reading and writing of HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Lectura y escritura de correo HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">HTML-kirjade lugemine ja kirjutamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Lukee ja kirjoittaa HTML-sähköpostiviestejä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Lecture et écriture de courrier électronique en HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite ler e escribir mensaxes usando HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">HTML levelek írása és olvasása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Lettura e scrittura di messaggi in HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">HTML 메시지를 읽고 쓸 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">HTML laiškų skaitymas ir rašymas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Lese og skrive HTML e-post.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">HTML-Nettbreven wiesen un schrieven.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lezen en schrijven van HTML-e-mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Czytanie i pisanie wiadomości HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Leitura e escrita de mensagens em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Leitura e gravação de e-mails em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр и написание писем в формате HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Čítanie a písanie HTML mailov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Branje in zapisovanje e-pošte v obliki HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Читање и писање ХТМЛ порука.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Čitanje i pisanje HTML poruka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Читање и писање ХТМЛ порука.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Čitanje i pisanje HTML poruka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Läsa och skriva HTML-brev.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">HTML posta yazma ve okuma.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість читання та створення повідомлень з використанням коду HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxReading and writing of HTML mail.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">阅读、撰写 HTML 邮件。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">讀寫 HTML 郵件。</li>
      <li>Ability to display plain text only from an HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إمكانيّة عرض النّصّ الصّرف فقط من بريد HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">L'habilitat de mostrar en text pla un correu HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'habilitat de mostrar en text pla un correu HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Von HTML-E-Mails kann nur der unformatierte Text angezeigt</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Ability to display plain text only from an HTML mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capacidad de mostrar exclusivamente el texto sin formato de un correo HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Võimalus kuvada HTML-kirja ainult lihttekstina</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Osaa näyttää HTML-viesteistä raakatekstin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Possibilité d'afficher un courrier électronique HTML en texte seul.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite mostrar só o texto simple de correo HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Sima szöveg megjelenítése HTML levélből.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Capacità di mostrare il solo testo semplice da un messaggio in formato HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">HTML 메시지의 텍스트만 표시할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kan vise bare ren tekst når posten er HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann HTML-Nettbreven as Eenfachtext wiesen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheid om alleen gewone tekst te laten zien uit een HTML-e-mail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość wyświetlania zwykłego tekstu w wiadomości HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidade de apresentar apenas o texto simples de uma mensagem em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidade de exibir apenas o texto simples de um e-mail em HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Функция просмотра текстового варианта из письма в формате HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosť zobraziť iba čistý text z HTML mailu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prikaz samo besedila iz e-pošte v obliki HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Приказивање само обичног текста из ХТМЛ порука.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Prikazivanje samo običnog teksta iz HTML poruka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Приказивање само обичног текста из ХТМЛ порука.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Prikazivanje samo običnog teksta iz HTML poruka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att bara visa vanlig text för ett HTML-brev.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Bir HTML postasından sadece düz metni gösterebilme.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість перегляду лише текстової частини з повідомлень у форматі HTML;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAbility to display plain text only from an HTML mail.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可以以纯文本的方式展示 HTML 邮件。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可以只顯示 HTML 郵件中的純文字部份。</li>
      <li>Allows you to receive and accept invitations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يسمح لك باستقبال الدّعوات وقبولها.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet rebre i acceptar invitacions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet rebre i acceptar invitacions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einladungen können gesendet und empfangen werden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Allows you to receive and accept invitations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Le permite recibir y aceptar invitaciones.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Võimalus saada ja vastu võtta kutseid</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Mahdollistaa kutsujen vastaanottamisen ja hyväksymisen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Permet de recevoir et accepter des invitations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite recibir e aceptar invitacións.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Meghívok fogadása és elfogadása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Permette di ricevere e accettare inviti.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">초대장을 받고 보낼 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Leidžia siųsti ir gauti pakvietimus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kan motta og akseptere invitasjoner.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Inladen laat sik dor mit kriegen un ok annehmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Stelt u in staat uitnodigingen te ontvangen en accepteren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość odbierania i przyjmowania zaproszeń.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Permite-lhe receber e aceitar convites.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permite-lhe receber e aceitar convites.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Получение и отправка приглашений;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Umožní vám prijať a prijímať pozvánky.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Omogoča prejemanje in sprejemanje povabil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Слање и прихватање позивница.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Slanje i prihvatanje pozivnica.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Слање и прихватање позивница.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Slanje i prihvatanje pozivnica.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Låter dig ta emot och acceptera inbjudningar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Davetleri alma ve kabul etmenize izin verir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість отримувати та приймати запрошення;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAllows you to receive and accept invitations.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">允许您接收并接受邀请。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可以接收與接受邀請。</li>
      <li>Integration with popular spam checkers, e.g. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">التّكامل مع فاحصات السّخام مثل سفّاح السّخام/SpamAssassin، وبوغوفلتر/Bogofilter وغيرها</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Integració amb els comprovadors de correu brossa més populars, p. ex., SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integració amb els comprovadors de correu brossa més populars, p. ex., SpamAssaren, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Integration von bekannten Spam-Filtern wie SpamAssassin, Bogofilter usw.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Integration with popular spam checkers, e.g. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración con verificadores de correo basura populares, p. ej., SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lõimimine levinumate rämpsposti kontrollijatega, nt. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter jne</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Integroituu suosittuihin roskapostitarkistimiin kuten SpamAssassiniin, Bogofilteriin jne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégration avec les vérificateurs de courrier indésirable courants comme SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Intégrase con comprobadores de correo lizo populares como SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Integráció népszerű spamszűrőkkel (például SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, stb).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Integrazione con noti sistemi di verifica dello spam, come ad es. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, ecc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">SpamAssassin, Bogofilter와 같은 스팸 검사 도구 연동</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Integrering med populære spamsjekkere, f.eks. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter osv.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Arbeidt mit faken bruukt Warven-Pröövprogrammen as SpamAssassin oder Bogofilter tosamen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integratie met populaire spamcheckers, bijv. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Integracja z powszechnymi programami wykrywającymi spam, np. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, itp.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração com as verificações de lixo electrónico, p.ex. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração com programas de verificação de spam, como o SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Интеграция с распространёнными системами фильтрации спама, например SpamAssassin, Bogofilter и другими;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrácia s populárnymi kontrolami spamu, napr. SmamAssassin, Bogofilter, atď.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira priljubljena orodja proti neželeni pošti, npr. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, itd.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Интеграција популарних оверивача спама, као што су Спамасасин, Богофилтер, итд.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Integracija popularnih overivača spama, kao što su SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, itd.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Интеграција популарних оверивача спама, као што су Спамасасин, Богофилтер, итд.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Integracija popularnih overivača spama, kao što su SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, itd.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrering med populära skräppostkontrollprogram, t.ex. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yaygın gereksiz posta (spam) denetleicileri ile tümleşik. Örn. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, vb.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">інтеграція з популярними системами захисту від небажаної кореспонденції, зокрема SpamAssassin, Bogofilter тощо;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegration with popular spam checkers, e.g. SpamAssassin, Bogofilter, etc.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">与流行垃圾邮件检查器的集成，如 SpamAssassin 和 Bogofilter 等。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">與常用的垃圾信檢查機制，如 SpamAssassin，Bogofilter 等整合。</li>
      <li>An optional spam probability meter can be displayed</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إمكانيّة اختياريّة لعرض عدّاد لاحتماليّة السّخام</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Es pot mostrar un mesurador de la probabilitat que es tracti de correu brossa</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Es pot mostrar un mesurador de la probabilitat que es tracti de correu brossa</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Es kann eine Anzeige der SPAM-Wahrscheinlichkeit einer E-Mail eingeblendet werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">An optional spam probability meter can be displayed</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Se puede mostrar un medidor opcional de probabilidad de correo basura</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Võimalus näidata rämpsposti tõenäosuse mõõdikut</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Haluttaessa osaa näyttää roskapostin todennäköisyysarvion</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Une mesure de la probabilité de courrier indésirable peut être affichée en option</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite mostrar un medidor da probabilidade de que unha mensaxe sexa correo lixo (optional).</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Opcionálisan spamvalószínűségi mérő megjelenítése</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Un misuratore opzionale della probabilità di spam può essere mostrato</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">추가적인 스팸 가능성 표시 도구</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kan vise, om ønskes, sannsynlighet for spam</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Köörwies lett sik en Maat wiesen, wo wohrschienlich de Nettbreef Warven is</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Een optionele waarschijnlijkheidsmeter voor spam kan getoond worden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość wyświetlania miernika prawdopodobieństwa, że to spam</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode ser apresentado um medidor de probabilidades de lixo electrónico</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pode ser apresentado um medidor de probabilidades de spam</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Может быть показан индикатор вероятности спама;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Je možné zobraziť voliteľný meter pravdepodobnosti spamu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prikazuje lahko dodatni merilnik za verjetnost, da je pošta neželena</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Опциони приказ мерача вероватноће спама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Opcioni prikaz merača verovatnoće spama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Опциони приказ мерача вероватноће спама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Opcioni prikaz merača verovatnoće spama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">En valfri sannolikhetsmätare för skräppost kan visas</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Görüntülenebilir, isteğe bağlı gereksiz posta ihtimali ölçümü</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість показу оцінки ймовірності небажаності повідомлення;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAn optional spam probability meter can be displayedxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可以显示一个可选的垃圾邮件可能性计量表。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可以選擇顯示垃圾信指數</li>
      <li>Powerful search and filter abilities</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إمكانيّات بحث وترشيح قويّة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Poderoses habilitats per a la cerca i filtratge</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Poderoses habilitats per a la busca i filtratge</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Leistungsfähige Such- und Filtermöglichkeiten</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Powerful search and filter abilities</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Potentes capacidades de búsqueda y filtrado</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Võimsad otsimis- ja filtreerimisvõimalused</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Sisältää tehokkaat haku- ja suodatusominaisuudet</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Capacités de recherche et filtrage puissants</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Potentes funcionalidades de buscar e filtrar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Hatékony keresési és szűrési képességek</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Notevoli capacità di ricerca e di filtraggio</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">강력한 검색 및 필터 기능</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Galingos paieškos ir filtravimo galimybės</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Slagkraftig søk- og filter-muligheter</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Deegte Söök un Filtern</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Krachtige zoek en filter mogelijkheden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zaawansowane możliwości wyszukiwania i filtrowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidades poderosas de pesquisa e filtragem</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidades pesquisa e filtragem poderosas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Широкие возможности поиска и фильтрации писем;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Silné schopnosti hľadania a filtrovania</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zmogljiv iskalnik in filtri</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Моћна претрага и филтрирање.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Moćna pretraga i filtriranje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Моћна претрага и филтрирање.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Moćna pretraga i filtriranje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kraftfulla sök- och filtreringsmöjligheter</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Güçlü arama ve filtreleme yetenekleri</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">потужні можливості з пошуку та фільтрування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPowerful search and filter abilitiesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">强大的搜索过滤能力</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">強大的搜尋與過濾功能</li>
      <li>Can import mail from many other clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إمكانيّة استيراد البريد من عدّة عملاء بريد</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pot importar el correu des de molts altres clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pot importar el correu des de molts altres clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">E-Mails können von vielen anderen Programmen importiert werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Can import mail from many other clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Puede importar correo de muchos otros clientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kirjade importimine paljudest muudest e-posti klientidest</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Voi tuoda viestejä monista muista ohjelmista</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Peut importer les messages de nombreux autres clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Pode importar datos de moitos outros clientes de correo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Levelek importálása számos más kliensből</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Può importare la posta da molti altri programmi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다른 클라이언트에서 메일 가져오기</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Gali importuoti paštą iš kitų programų</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kan importere e-post fra mange andre klienter</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann Nettbreven ut en Barg anner Nettpostprogrammen importeren</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan e-mail importeren uit vele andere clients</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość importowania poczty z innych programów pocztowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Poderá importar o correio a partir de muitos outros clientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importação de e-mails de muitos outros clientes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Возможен импорт писем из множества других почтовых клиентов;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Môže importovať mail z mnohých iných klientov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Lahko uvozi e-pošto iz drugih odjemalcev</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Увоз поште из многих других клијената.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Uvoz pošte iz mnogih drugih klijenata.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Увоз поште из многих других клијената.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Uvoz pošte iz mnogih drugih klijenata.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan importera brev från många andra program</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Diğer birçok istemciden postaları içe aktarabilme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість імпортувати дані пошти з багатьох інших програм для роботи з електронною поштою;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan import mail from many other clientsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可以从许多其它客户端导入邮件</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可以從其它郵件程式中匯入信件</li>
      <li>Searching in IMAP folders fully supported</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">البحث في مجلّدات IMAP مدعوم بالكامل</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">La cerca a les carpetes IMAP està totalment implementada</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">La busca a les carpetes IMAP està totalment implementada</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Suche in IMAP-Ordnern wird vollständig unterstützt</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Searching in IMAP folders fully supported</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Búsqueda en carpetas IMAP completamente implementada</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täielik IMAP kaustades otsimise toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee hakuja IMAP-kansioista täysin</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Recherche des dossiers IMAP complètement prise en charge</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite buscar en cartafoles IMAP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Keresés IMAP mappákban</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricerca in cartelle IMAP pienamente supportata</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">IMAP 폴더 내 검색</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Full støtte for søking i IMAP-mapper</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Söken binnen IMAP-Ornern warrt heel ünnerstütt</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">In IMAP-mappen zoeken wordt volledig ondersteund</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">W pełni obsługiwane wyszukiwanie w katalogach IMAP</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A pesquisa nas pastas de IMAP é totalmente suportada</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte completo para pesquisa em pastas IMAP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полная поддержка поиска в папках IMAP;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hľadanie v IMAP priečinokoch je plne podporované</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Polno podpira iskanje po mapah IMAP</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Потпуна подршка за претрагу по ИМАП фасциклама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Potpuna podrška za pretragu po IMAP fasciklama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Потпуна подршка за претрагу по ИМАП фасциклама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Potpuna podrška za pretragu po IMAP fasciklama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständigt stöd för sökning i IMAP-korgar</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">IMAP klasörlerinde arama tamamen desteklenmektedir</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка повноцінного пошуку у теках IMAP;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSearching in IMAP folders fully supportedxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">完全支持在 IMAP 文件夹内进行搜索</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">完整支援在 IMAP 資料夾中搜尋</li>
      <li>Highly integrated with other Kontact components</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">متكامل مع مكوّنات «تراسلك» الأخرى</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Altament integrat amb els altres components del Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Altament integrat amb els altres components del Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Gut in andere Kontact-Componenten integriert</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Highly integrated with other Kontact components</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Altamente integrado con otros componentes de Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Tugev lõimimine teiste Kontacti komponentidega</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Integroituu erinomaisesti muihin Kontactin osiin</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégration poussée avec les autres composants de la suite Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Intégrase perfectamente con outros compoñentes de Kontact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Integráció más Kontact komponensekkel</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Molto integrato con altri componenti di Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Kontact 구성 요소와 강력한 통합</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Sterkt integrert med andre Kontact-komponenter</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Arbeidt drang mit anner Kontact-Komponenten tosamen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hoge graad van integratie met andere componenten van Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wysoce zintegrowane z innymi składnikami Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Altamente integrado com os outros componentes do Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Altamente integrado com os outros componentes do Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Тесная интеграция с другими компонентами Kontact;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vysoko integrovaný s inými komponentmi Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Se zelo dobro vključi v druge sestavne dele paketa Kontact</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Висока интеграција са осталим компонентама Контакта.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Visoka integracija sa ostalim komponentama Kontacta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Висока интеграција са осталим компонентама Контакта.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Visoka integracija sa ostalim komponentama Kontacta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Helt integrerad med andra Kontact-komponenter</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Diğer Kontact bileşenleri ile yüksek derecede tümleşik</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">високий рівень інтеграції з іншими компонентами Kontact;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxHighly integrated with other Kontact componentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">与其它 Kontact 组件高度集成</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">與其他 Kontact 組件高度整合</li>
      <li>Encrypted password saving in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">حفظ كلمات المرور معمّاة في «محفظتك»</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desa la contrasenya encriptada al KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Guarda la contrasenya encriptada al KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Verschlüsselte Speicherung von Passwörtern in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Encrypted password saving in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Contraseñas cifradas guardadas en KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Krüptitud paroolide salvestame KDE turvalaekasse</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Voi tallentaa salasanat salattuna KDE:n lompakkoon</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Enregistrement des mots de passe chiffré dans KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite gardar os contrasinais cifrados usando KWallet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Jelszavak mentése titkosítottan a KWalletben</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Salvataggio di password cifrate in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">KWallet을 사용하여 암호 저장</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Lagrer krypterte passord i KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Passwöör warrt verslötelt binnen KWallet wohrt</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Opslaan van versleuteld wachtwoord in KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Szyfrowane zapisywanie haseł w KPortfelu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gravação das senhas encriptadas na KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Salvamento das senhas criptografadas no KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Сохранение паролей в зашифрованном виде с помощью KWallet;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ukladanie šifrovaných hesiel v KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Šifrirano shranjevanje gesel v KWallet</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Уписивање шифрованих лозинки у К‑новчаник.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Upisivanje šifrovanih lozinki u K‑novčanik.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Уписивање шифрованих лозинки у К‑новчаник.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Upisivanje šifrovanih lozinki u K‑novčanik.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Krypterat lösenord sparas i plånboken</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">KWallet (KDE Cüzdan) içerisine şifreli parola kaydetme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">зберігання зашифрованих реєстраційних даних за допомогою KWallet;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEncrypted password saving in KWalletxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Kwallet 中保存加密密码</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">將密碼加密並儲存在 KWallet</li>
      <li>Flagging and tagging of messages to aid sorting and recovery of information</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تعليم الرّسائل ووسمها للمساعدة في فرز المعلومات واستعادتها</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Marca i etiqueta els missatges per ajudar a la classificació i recuperació de la informació</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Marca i etiqueta els missatges per ajudar a la classificació i recuperació de la informació</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Nachrichten können markiert werden, um das Sortieren und Auffinden von Informationen zu erleichtern</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Flagging and tagging of messages to aid sorting and recovery of information</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Marcado y etiquetado de mensajes para ayudar a la ordenación y recuperación de información</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kirjade sildistamine ja märgistamine nende hõlpsamaks sortimiseks ja teabe leidmiseks</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Sisältää viestien merkintä ja luokittelu lajittelun ja tiedon palautuksen helpottamiseksi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Ajout de drapeaux et d'étiquettes aux messages pour faciliter le tri et la récupération d'informations</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite marcar as mensaxes con marcas ou etiquetas para axudar a ordenar e recuperar información.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Üzenetek jelölése és címkézése a rendezés és keresés megkönnyítésére</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Marcatura dei messaggi per aiutare l'ordinamento e il recupero delle informazioni</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">메시지 정렬 및 빠른 찾기를 위해서 메시지에 태그 및 깃발 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Flagger og setter etikett på meldinger for enklere sortering og informasjonshenting</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Narichten laat sik markeren un dor laat sik Slötelwöör na tofögen; de Narichten laat sik denn beter sorteren un Informatschonen beter finnen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vlaggen en tags aanbrengen bij berichten om te helpen bij sorteren en herstel van informatie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Oflagowywanie i znaczenie wiadomości w celu wspomożenia ich szeregowania i uzyskiwania informacji</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Marcação e classificação de mensagens para ajudar a ordenar e a recuperar informações</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Marcação e classificação de mensagens para ajudar a ordenar e recuperar informações</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Письмам можно присваивать различные состояния и метки;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Označovanie a značkovanie správ na podporu triedenia a využitia informácií</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Označevanje sporočil, ki pomaga pri razvrščanju in obnovitvi podatkov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Означавање порука ради лакшег разврставања и доступности информација.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Označavanje poruka radi lakšeg razvrstavanja i dostupnosti informacija.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Означавање порука ради лакшег разврставања и доступности информација.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Označavanje poruka radi lakšeg razvrstavanja i dostupnosti informacija.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flaggning och etikettering av brev för att hjälpa till att sortera och återhämta information</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sıralama ve bilgi kurtarımı yardımı için ileti bayraklama ve etiketleme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість додавання прапорців і міток до повідомлень з метою спрощення упорядковування та відновлення інформації;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFlagging and tagging of messages to aid sorting and recovery of informationxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可以对邮件做标记、打标签以协助进行信息的排序和恢复</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對信件加上旗標或標籤，以便排序與找到資訊</li>
      <li>Supports mailing list management features</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم ميزات إدارة القوائم البريديّة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementa característiques per a la gestió de les llistes de correu</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Implementa característiques per a la gestió de les llistes de correu</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt die Verwaltung von Mailinglisten</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports mailing list management features</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa características de gestión de listas de correo</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Postiloendite haldamise toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee sähköpostilistojen hallinnan ominaisuuksia</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Fonctions de gestion de listes de diffusion</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Fornece funcionalidades de xestión de listas de correo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Levelezőlista-kezelési szolgáltatások támogatása</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per le funzioni di gestione delle mailing list</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">메일링 리스트 관리 기능 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Støtter funksjoner for e-postlister</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Funkschonen för't Plegen vun Nettpostlisten sünd al inbuut</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt functies voor discussielijstbeheer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość zarządzania listą dyskusyjną</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta funcionalidades de gestão de listas de correio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a funcionalidades de gerenciamento de listas de discussão</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Функции для работы со списками рассылки;</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora funkcií správy mailing listov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira upravljanje dopisnih seznamov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Управљање поштанском листом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Upravljanje poštanskom listom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Управљање поштанском листом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Upravljanje poštanskom listom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder funktioner för hantering av sändlistor</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Posta listesi yönetim özelliklerini destekler</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка можливостей з керування повідомленнями зі списків листування;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports mailing list management featuresxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持邮件列表管理功能</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援郵件論壇管理功能</li>
      <li>Can replace text smilies with emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يمكنه استبدال الابتسامات النّصيّة بأخرى رسوميّة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pot substituir les cares de text amb emoticones</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pot substituir les cares de text amb emoticones</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kann Text-Smileys durch Emoticons ersetzen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Can replace text smilies with emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Puede remplazar sonrisas de texto con emoticones</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Teksti-emotikonide asendamine pilt-emotikonidega</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Voi korvata tekstihymiöt kuvakkeilla</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Peut remplacer les smileys par des émoticônes</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Pode substituír as iconas de texto por imaxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Szöveges hangulatjelek cseréje hangulatikonokra</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Può sostituire le faccine di testo con emoticon</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">텍스트 이모티콘을 그래픽으로 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kan erstatte tekst-smilefjes med emotikoner</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann för Text-Snuten Biller insetten</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan smilies in de tekst vervangen door emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość zastępowania buziek tekstowych emotikonami</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode substituir ícones emotivos de texto por gráficos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Substituição carinhas de texto por emoticons</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vie nahradiť textové smajlíky emotikonmi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Lahko zamenja besedilne smeške z izraznimi ikonami</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Опциона замена текстуалних смешкова емотиконима.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Opciona zamena tekstualnih smeškova emotikonima.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Опциона замена текстуалних смешкова емотиконима.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Opciona zamena tekstualnih smeškova emotikonima.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan ersätta textsmilisar med ikoner</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Metin yüz ifadelerini simgelere dönüştürebilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість заміни текстових емоційок (смайликів) зображеннями;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan replace text smilies with emoticonsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可以使用表情符号替换文字 smilies</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可以用表情符號取代文字式的表情符號</li>
      <li>Displays the sender's picture or avatar if present in the address book</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض صورة المرسل أو صورة أفاتار إن وُجدت في دفتر العناوين</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mostra la imatge o avatar del remitent si està present a la llibreta d'adreces</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mostra la imatge o avatar del remitent si està present a la llibreta d'adreces</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zeigt das Bild oder den Avatar des Absenders an, sofern im Adressbuch eines vorhanden ist</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Displays the sender's picture or avatar if present in the address book</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Muestra la imagen o avatar del remitente si está presente en la libreta de direcciones</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Saatja pildi või avatari kuvamine, kui see leidub aadressiraamatus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Näyttää lähettäjän kuvan tai avatarin, jos se löytyy osoitekirjasta</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affiche une photo ou un avatar de l'expéditeur s'il sont disponibles dans le carnet d'adresse</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Mostra a imaxe do remitente se este está presente no caderno de enderezos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">A küldő képének megjelenítése, ha a címjegyzékben megtalálható</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Mostra l'immagine o l'avatar del mittente se disponibile in rubrica</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">주소록과 연동된 보낸 사람의 사진 및 아바타 표시</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Viser avsenders bilde eller avatar hvis det finnes i adresseboka</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Wiest den Senner sien Bild oder Bildteken, wenn dat een binnen dat Adressbook gifft</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Toont de foto of avatar van de afzender indien aanwezig in het adresboek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie zdjęcia nadawcy lub awatara, jeśli jest dostępny w książce adresowej</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mostra a imagem ou avatar do remetente, caso esteja presente no livro de endereços</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Mostra a imagem ou avatar do remetente, caso esteja presente no livro de endereços</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zobrazí obrázok odosielateľa alebo avatar, ak je dostupny v adresári kontaktov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prikaže sliko pošiljatelja ali podobo, če je prisotna v imeniku</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Приказ слике или аватара пошиљаоца, ако их има у адресару.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Prikaz slike ili avatara pošiljaoca, ako ih ima u adresaru.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Приказ слике или аватара пошиљаоца, ако их има у адресару.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Prikaz slike ili avatara pošiljaoca, ako ih ima u adresaru.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visar avsändarens bild eller avatar om den finns i adressboken</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Adres defterinde mevcutsa gönderenin fotoğrafı veya profil resmi gösterilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість показу знімка або аватара відправника, якщо його визначено у адресній книзі;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplays the sender's picture or avatar if present in the address bookxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">如果在地址簿中存在的话，显示发送者的图片或者 avatar。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">如果通訊錄裡有的話，可以顯示發信者的頭像</li>
      <li>Supports X-Face (b/w pictures in messages)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم X-Face (صور بالأبيض والأسود في الرّسائل)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet X-Face (imatges en b/n als missatges)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet X-Face (imatges en b/n als missatges)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt X-Face (Schwarzweiß-Bilder in Nachrichten)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports X-Face (b/w pictures in messages)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa X-Face (imágenes en blanco y negro en los mensajes)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">X-Face'i toetus (mustvalged pildid kirjades)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee X-Face-ominaisuutta (viesteissä olevat mustavalkokuvat)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prend en charge X-Face (images noir et blanc dans l'en-tête des messages)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatíbel con X-Face (mensaxes en branco e negro nas mensaxes).</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">X-Face támogatása (fekete-fehér képek az üzenetekben)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta X-Face (immagini in bianco e nero nei messaggi)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">X-Face 지원(메시지 내 흑백 사진)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Støtter X-Face (s/hv bilder i meldinger)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ünnerstütt X-Face (Swattwitt-Biller binnen Narichten)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt X-Face (z/w plaatjes in berichten)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa X-Face (zdjęcia czarno białe w wiadomościach)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta o X-Face (imagens a p/b nas mensagens)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta a X-Face (imagens em preto e branco nas mensagens)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje X-Face (č/b obrázky v správach)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira X-Face (črno-bele slike v sporočilih)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за X-Face (црно‑беле слике у порукама).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za X-Face (crno‑bele slike u porukama).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за X-Face (црно‑беле слике у порукама).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za X-Face (crno‑bele slike u porukama).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder X-Face (svartvita bilder i brev)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">X-Face (iletilerde siyah beyaz resimler) desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка X-Face (чорно-білих зображень у повідомленнях);</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports X-Face (b/w pictures in messages)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持 X-Face（邮件信息中的头像）</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援 X-Face（信件裡顯示黑白頭像）</li>
      <li>Compression of attachments</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">ضغط المرفقات</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">La compressió dels adjunts</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">La compressió dels adjunts</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Komprimierung von Anhängen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Compression of attachments</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Compresión de adjuntos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Manuste tihendamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee liitteiden pakkaamista</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Compression des pièces jointes</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite comprimir os ficheiros anexos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Mellékletek tömörítése</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Compressione degli allegati</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">첨부 파일 압축</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">Priedų spaudimas</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Komprimerer vedlegg        </li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Komprimeren vun Bilagen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Compressie van bijlagen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pakowanie załączników</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Compressão dos anexos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Compressão dos anexos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kompresia príloh</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Stiskanje prilog</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Компресовање прилога.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Kompresovanje priloga.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Компресовање прилога.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Kompresovanje priloga.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Komprimering av bilagor</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Eklerin sıkıştırılması</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">можливість стискання долучень безпосередньо з вікна програми;</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCompression of attachmentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">附件的压缩</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">附件壓縮</li>
      <li>KMail supports Groupware functionality.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم «بريدك» وظيفة البرمجيّات التّعاونيّة.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">El KMail permet el treball en grup (groupware).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KMail permet el treball en grup (groupware).</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">KMail unterstützt Groupware-Funktionalität.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">KMail supports Groupware functionality.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">KMail implementa funcionalidades de colaboración.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Grupitöö võimaluste toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">KMail tukee työryhmätoimintoja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités de logiciel de groupe de travail.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">KMail é compatíbel con funcionalidades de xestión de grupos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">A KMail támogatja a csoportmunka funkciókat is.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">KMail supporta funzionalità di groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">KMail은 그룹웨어 기능을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="lt">KMail palaiko Groupware galimybes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">KMail støtter Gruppevarefunksjonalitet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">KMail ünnerstütt Arbeitkoppel-Funkschonen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">KMail ondersteunt Groupware functionaliteit.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa funkcjonalności Groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">O KMail suporta as funcionalidades de trabalho em grupo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a funcionalidades de Groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">KMail podporuje funkcionalitu Groupware.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira programe za skupinsko delo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">К‑пошта подржава групверску функционалност.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑pošta podržava grupversku funkcionalnost.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑пошта подржава групверску функционалност.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑pošta podržava grupversku funkcionalnost.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kmail stöder grupprogramfunktioner.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">KMail, Groupware işlevselliğini destekler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">підтримка роботи у групах.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxKMail supports Groupware functionality.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">Kmail 支持 Groupware 功能。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">KMail 支援群組功能。</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmail2</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdepim/kmail2/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kmail.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmail</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
